I'm so excited I'm redoing this video
because I just have so much to tell you
I am streaming from a limousine
otherwise known as subu this is my zuuu
and I'm like living my dream here by
working out of my car is and there's so
much to show you I I can show you like
how I did the thing I'm going to sleep
in here I have an awning we're going to
be have a little table here so we can
like have a mic out so random people are
like what the hell is going on I'm like
why don't you have a seat and talk to me
on the rwx Rob
podcasts on the road morning boost on
the road the morning radio show on the
road do you want to join me I'm going to
snipe you somebody said somebody called
it out I'm going to reverse sniping if
you're in my community I'm gonna find
you and I'm going to snipe you yeah I am
so be very
careful but if you want to snipe me
please come find me come sit down have
some you know sit down and let's let's
let's talk let's talk let's do the thing
uh we get talk about whatever uh you can
be on the art raw morning boost Morning
Show which I have now committed to do
every day from the car which is cool
because now I mean I have to do it
relatively close to Wi-Fi right now
because I don't have the starlink yet
it's coming it's going to be here in
like two two weeks or so but when the
starlink is right here I mean it's just
I'm going to be able to just go anywhere
so we're going to like pull we're going
to like roll on up to a random Starbucks
or a random you know Park someplace and
look we're just going to set set it up
and I mean hell I might even have
banners made I might even have banners
made I'll put a little Banner RBX Rob
and they'll be like oh I know you I saw
you on Twitch and then they can come and
sit down and we'll talk we'll talk about
all kinds of things but we're generally
going to focus on you know what it means
to become a technologist today and why
you might want to be a technologist
we're going to talk a lot about bikes
and IRL living and being on the road and
all that stuff and yeah I'll probably do
some dual streams with like other people
do the IRL thing assuming they deem me
worthy to be seen with them yeah I'm I'm
winking at you
Trevor but you know we're we're GNA be
all over and so we're it's great we're
going to go see the Grand Canyon we're
going to start in North Carolina we're
going to start on the beaches of North
Carolina we're we're gonna I mean it's
just it's just going to be fantastic I
am so excited um and this is the first
day this is the first day of the morning
Boost from Subaru I have committed to
moving all of my gear into the Subaru um
otherwise sometimes known as subido
depends on the day but yeah we're gonna
we're g this is all going to get
strapped down uh you can stay tuned for
me for that but the the the morning boo
show with the music and stuff is going
to be from here if you want to watch all
the random you know me setting up and
some the occasional bike stream guess
what else I can do I can actually send
the IRL stream not even kidding
to through this I did it yesterday you
know you know my IRL pack that I put on
my back and I put on the bicycle it
actually goes through my Mac now I'm
going to do a separate video just about
the Mac it's absolutely amazing and I
know shout out to the people at micro
micro center I did not post a video
about them because I want to make a
better one but the Microcenter people
set me up we're going to talk about that
in
fact here we go come on you're not going
to do it now why aren't you doing okay
there we go
so it is glorious I am so excited please
join me here is a little music hopefully
it won't get me
demonetized bye-bye